Guide to the Tillie Olsen Papers, 1930-1990 M0667
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 11. Published works
  Series XI, the final series, contains different published editions of Tell Me a Riddle, Silences, and Yonnondio: From the Thirties. A few copies are of foreign editions, and some editions have her corrections in the margins. Also within this series are audio cassettes of various readings and talks, including tapes of her reading Tell Me a Riddle and "The Strike."
  - Tell Me a Riddle: 14 editions (7 foreign) (Box 49)
  - Yonnondio: From the Thirties: 6 editions (2 foreign) (Box 49)
  - Silences: 5 editions (2 foreign) (Box 49)
  - Life in the Iron Mills - Rebecca Harding Davis (1edition) (Box 49)
- Series 12. Audiovisual materials
  - "Authors in America," Swedish TV: Interview with Tillie Olsen, July 17, 1984 (Box 49)
  - Audio Track from Swedish TV, copied, 9/17/85 (Box 49)
  - Walker, Olsen, Caldicott: Grace Cathedral, March 1982 (Box 49)
  - "Novels into Film," Tillie Olsen:, 11-Nov-84 (Box 49)
  - Tillie Olsen reads Tell Me a Riddle, 21-Nov-63 (Box 49)
  - Tillie Olsen reads Tell Me a Riddle, April 20-22, 1978 (Box 49)
  - Tillie Olsen reads "The Strike" (Box 49)
  - Tell Me a Riddle: Foreign recording (Box 49)
  - "Tell Me A Riddle" book reading, March 31, 1987; (2 cassettes) (Box 49)
  - "Tillie Olsen Day", (2 casettes) (Box 49)
  - Tell Me a Riddle - reading, Missouri Western S.C. (Box 49)
  - Tillie Olsen reading:, undated (Box 49)
  - Unidentified recording (Box 49)
- Series 13. Photographs (accession 2009-041), Series 13
  - Tillie Olsen photographs: early life (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Tillie Olsen photographs: Lerner family (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Tillie Olsen photographs: prior and during World War II (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Tillie Olsen photographs: family and children (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Tillie Olsen photographs: Jack and Tillie (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Tillie Olsen photographs: Tillie as political person (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Tillie Olsen photographs: Tillie portraits (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Tillie Olsen photographs: awards (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Tillie Olsen photographs: life as writer (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Tillie Olsen photographs: professional portraits (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Tillie Olsen photographs: last year of life (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Tillie Olsen photographs: Tillie with colleagues (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Tillie Olsen photographs: images on CD (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Tillie Olsen photographs: detailed inventory (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Series 14: Accession 2009-220
  - Family Correspondence
    - Family letters: Cory (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Family letters: Ericka (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Family letters: Eva (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Family letters: Gene (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Family letters: Harry and Clare (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Family letters: Jann (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Family letters: Jesse (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Family letters: Jessica (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Family letters: Josh (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Family letters: Julie (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Family letters: Karla (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Family letters: Laurie Olsen (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Family letters: Laurie Olsen (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Family letters: Lil (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Family letters: Leon (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Family letters: Margaret (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Family letters: Matt (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Family letters: Morrie (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Family letters: parents (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Family letters: Rebekah and Lynn (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Family letters: Reeva (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Family letters: Toby (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Family letters: Vicky and Monty (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Family letters: Yetta (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Family letters: miscellaneous (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Jack Olsen to Tillie Olsen, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Jack Olsen to Tillie Olsen, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Jack Olsen to Tillie Olsen, World War II (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Jack Olsen to Tillie Olsen, World War II (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Jack Olsen to Tillie Olsen, World War II (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Jack Olsen to Tillie Olsen, World War II (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Jack Olsen to Tillie Olsen, World War II (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Tillie Olsen to Jack Olsen, World War II (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Jack Olsen to Tillie Olsen, 1960's (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Tillie Olsen to Jack Olsen, ca. 1968 [MacDowell Colony] (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Tillie Olsen to Jack Olsen, ca. 1968 [MacDowell Colony] (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Tillie Olsen to Jack Olsen, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Tillie Olsen to Jack Olsen, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Tillie Olsen to Jack Olsen, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Tillie Olsen to Karla Olsen, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Tillie Olsen to Julie Olsen, 1979 (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Tillie Olsen to Laurie Olsen, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Tillie Olsen to daughters, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Family correspondence: Tillie Olsen, outgoing (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Family correspondence: Tillie Olsen, incoming (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Family correspondence: Tillie Olsen, incoming (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: miscellaneous family letters, fragments (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Laurie Olsen, miscellaneous incoming (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Laurie Olsen, miscellaneous outgoing (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - Family correspondence: Tillie Olsen, incoming from unnamed daughter (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Olsen family: miscellaneous personal letters, incoming: 2003-2005 (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Olsen family: miscellaneous personal letters (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Personal correspondence: Karla Olsen, incoming and outgoing (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Personal correspondence: Julie Olsen, incoming (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Personal correspondence: Jack Olsen, incoming (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Personal correspondence: Jack Olsen, outgoing (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous notes/writings/poems re. Jack Olsen (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Abraham Jevons Goldfarb correspondence (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Abraham Jevons Goldfarb / Nahman correspondence (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Karla Olsen, incoming and outgoing correspondence (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Kathie Olsen, incoming and outgoing correspondence (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Laurie Olsen, incoming and outgoing correspondence (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Julie Olsen, miscellaneous (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Family Memorabilia: biographical material, photographs
    - Awards/Diplomas (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Central High School: 1929 yearbook and various memorabilia (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Lerner family genealogy (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Family memorabilia (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Abraham Olshansky: certificate of naturalization, 1923 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - J. Olshansky: early school writing [ca. 1927-1928] (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Gene Lerner: miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Harry Lerner: miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Ida Lerner: miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Yetta Lerner: miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Samuel Lerner: miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Toby Edwards: miscellaneous (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Jack Olsen: memorabilia (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Jack Olsen: death and memorial (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Laurie Olsen: memorabilia (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Jesse/Laura Olsen material (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Karla memorabilia (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous Tillie memorabilia (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Olsen Family photographs (includes WW II Jack Olsen photograph taken just after battle) (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Tillie Olsen chronology/biography (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Items from Tillie Olsen's wall (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous family materials (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Tillie Olsen driver's license (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Leon Olson memorabilia (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Rebekah Olsen memorabilia (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Reeva Olson memorabilia (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Tillie Olsen Warden report form (World War II activism) (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - John Olsen: Veteran's Administration (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Jack Olsen (?): unidentified artwork (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Tributes to Henry Lerner, Tillie Olsen's brother (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Memorabilia: Olshansky (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Material regarding Sam Lawrence (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Jack Olsen material: workcards, strike cards, passport, union cards, etc. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Jack Olsen material: workcards, strike cards, passport, union cards, etc. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Sam Lerner: straight blade razors and strop (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Family genealogy information (Nebraska land plot), photocopy (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous property contracts (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - General Correspondence
    - Correspondence: Aberlin, Betty (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Allen, Steve (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Arnold, Katherine (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Ausubel, Bobbi (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Ballantyne, Sheila (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Bonfeild, Lynn (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Boucher, Sandy (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Bryant, Dorothy (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Burford, Jim (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Carroll, Peter (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Catacolos, Rose (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Chen, Kevin (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Chown, Miriam and Paul (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Cobble, Sue (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Coiner, Constance (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Coiner, Virginia (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Coles, Bob (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Daigon, Ruth (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Davenport, Kiana (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Davis, Martha (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Dawahare, Anthony (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Diamond, Arlyn (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Di Prima, Diane (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Doro, Sue (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Doubiago, Sharon (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Falk, Candace (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Ferguson, Mary Anne (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Finneran, Kathleen (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Ford, Conny (Box 1, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: Frye, Joanne (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Goad, Rosemary (Box 1, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: Green, Hannah (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Griffin, Susan (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Hedges, Elaine (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Henry, Dewitt (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Hershey, Annie (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Howe, Florence (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Hughes, Mary Gray (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Irwin, Doria (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Jacobson, Joanne (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Johnson, Miriam (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Kaye, George (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Kessting, Mabel (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Kingston, Maxine Hong (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Klausenstock, Oskar (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Konecky, Edith (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Lawrence, Margaret (Box 2, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Lawrence, Sam (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Lazarre, Jane (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Levin, Tobe (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Lynn, Sue (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Maguire, Ruth (Box 2, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Margolin, Malcolm (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Markson, Elaine (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Maulpied, Debby de (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Maynord, Valerie (Box 2, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Mazali, Rela (Box 2, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: McCann, Richard (Box 2, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: McCarriston, Linda (Box 2, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: McPheron, Bill (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: Meyer, Howard (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Meyers, Odette (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Middlebrook, Diane (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Miller, Nolan (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Miner, Valerie (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Moers, Ellen (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Murray, Aife (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Murray, Janet (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Nagarajan, Vijaya (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Nasan, Thelma (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Noble, Yvonne (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Orr, Elaine (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Ozick, Cynthia (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Paley, Grace (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Patta, Margaret de (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Pineda, Cecile (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Pineda, Marrianne (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Poli, Sara (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Porter, Nancy (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Pratt, Linda (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Reid, Panthea (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Rich, Adrienne (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Robinson, Dorothy (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence: Robinson, Lillian (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence: Rosenfelt, Debby (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - Correspondence: Russell, Diarmvid (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Correspondence: Sankey, Debby and Maury (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence: Sarachild, Kathie (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence: Sexton, Anne [photocopies] (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence: Sexton, Linda Grey (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence: Shea, Renee (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence: Smith, April (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Correspondence: Spacks, Barry (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Correspondence: Stegner, Wallace (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Stern, Marjorie (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Stone, Ruth (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Stubbs, Imogen (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Tovish, Red (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Walker, Alice [photocopies] (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Walker, Mike (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Warshaw, Mary (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Watanabe, Kazuko (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Webb, Mary (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Weisman, Adele (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Wells, Marilyn (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Whitehall-Smith, Carol (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Wilson, J. J. (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Winslow, Joyce (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Wixson, Douglas (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence: Wong, Nellie (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence: Wright, Richard (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence: Wynne, Pat (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence: Yalom, Marilyn (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence: Yamagrhara, Shin (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence: Zandy, Janet (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Rae Schochet and Ethel Gordon, 1932-1940's (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Rae Schochet and Ethel Gordon, 1940's (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence: Rae Schochet and Ethel Gordon, 19640's (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence: Rae Schochet and Ethel Gordon, 19640's (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Fran (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence: A/B (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence, A/B (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence, C/D (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence, E/F (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence, G/H (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence, I/J (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence, K/L (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence, K/L (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence, M/N (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence, O/P/Q (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence, R/S (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence, R/S (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence, T/U/V (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence, W/X/Y/Z (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence (not filed) (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence: Sue (?) to Tillie Olsen, ca. 1933 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence: Dot and Aaron Braude to Tillie (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Phyllis Koestenbaum to Tillie (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Elisa (?) to Tillie (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Jane's (various) to Tillie (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Marilyn's (various) to Tillie (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence, ca. 1930-1957 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Richard Elman (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Richard Scowcraft [photocopies and originals] (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence: unknown (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Marion [?] to Tillie Olsen, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous personal correspondence (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Tillie Olsen, outgoing correspondence (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Tillie Olsen, outgoing correspondence (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Tillie Olsen, miscellaneous incoming correspondence (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Tillie Olsen, miscellaneous incoming correspondence (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Tillie and Jack Olsen, miscellaneous incoming correspondence (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Tillie Olsen/Sandy Boucher correspondence (photocopies) (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Tillie Olsen/Dick Elman correspondence (photocopies) (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Tillie Olsen/Mary Gray Hughes correspondence (photocopies) (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Tillie Olsen/Edith Konecky correspondence (photocopies) (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Tillie Olsen/Nolan Miller correspondence (photocopies) (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Tillie Olsen/Mary Jane Moffat correspondence (photocopies) (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Tillie Olsen/Marge Piercy correspondence (photocopies) (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Tillie Olsen/Marianna Tovish correspondence (photocopies) (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence re. Tillie Olsen (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - "Josie"/Katherine Anne Porter correspondence (photocopies) (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous correspondence (unknown) (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Anne Sexton / Tillie Olsen correspondence [photocopies] (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Fan mail to Tillie (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Student correspondence to Tillie (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Student correspondence to Tillie (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Stanford University course: misc. student correspondence (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - University of Nebraska correspondence (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Dorothy Healy / Al (?) correspondence (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - "A letter to Leo" [photocopy] (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Michael Furmanovsky correspondence to Jack Olsen with manuscript, "Chapter Eight: Inside the Los Angeles Communist Party" (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Misc. correrspondence re. Jack Olsen's death (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Incoming Correspondence / sympathy notes (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Incoming Correspondence / sympathy notes (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous postcards (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous postcards (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous postcards (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous postcards (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous postcards (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous postcards (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Incoming correspondence (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Business Correspondence/Permissions/Agreements
    - Permissions signed by Tillie Olsen, ca. 1980-1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Business correspondence, A/B (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Business correspondence, C/D (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Business correspondence, E/F (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Business correspondence, G/H/I/J (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - Business correspondence, K/L (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Business correspondence, M/N (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Business correspondence, O/P/Q (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Business correspondence, R/S (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Business correspondence, T/U/V (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Business correspondence, W/X/Y/Z (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Business correspondence re. Requa (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Misc. Business correspondence: appointments/festivals/permissions (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Misc. Business correspondence: permissions (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Business correspondence re. publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Business contracts and agreements (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous business correspondence (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Middlebrook-Olsen agreement (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Elaine Markson contracts (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Tillie's Writings: publications, fragments, notes, interviews
    - Tillie Olsen: miscellaneous notes/documents (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Early poetry [circa 1929?] (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Writings: poetry fragments (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Early verse (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Quotes and poems by others, re-written by Tillie Olsen (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Early prose [photocopies] (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous fragments (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, 1968-2003 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Corrections to "Yonnondio" (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - "Motherhood," makings (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous notes and fragments, circa 1980s (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Writings [photocopies from Stanford] (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, [ca. January - March, 1984] (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous fragments: circa 1930s (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous fragments: "self" (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated [Photocopies] (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous writings/notes, re. Alice after split (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Miscellaneous notes [photocopies], MacDowell (?) (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous fragments: "very important to Tillie" (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Miscellaneous fragments, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)